35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentifie
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Men on a dock on a lake], 7
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Men on a dock on a lake], 8
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: People rowing boats on a lake], 9
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Table by a pool], 10
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Rolling hills], 11
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Side of a house], 12
  - Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places], undated; 2 (Box 1592)
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Garden], 1
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Baby in a gate], 2
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Baby in a gate], 3
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Baby in garden], 4
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Side of house], 5
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Side of house], 6
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: A white house], 7
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Person sitting in a garden with a dog], 8
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Person looking at flowers in garden], 9
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Person sitting in a garden with a dog], 10
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Clouds], 11
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: People sitting on porch with two dogs], 12
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Frog], 13
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: Man sitting outside of a building, reading a letter with other men standing around him], 14
  - Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica - from Cape Town to McMurdo Station, 1963): slide 1: Rear Admiral James R. Reedy and Lowell Thomas prepare to board one of the LC-130s of VX-6, Air Development Squadron, for the non-stop flight from Cape Town, South Africa to McMurdo Station, Antarctica; slide 2: Crews of both LC-130s shortly before departure on historic flight (non-stop) from Cape Town, South Africa to McMurdo Station, Antarctica. Left to right: front row - Lieutenant Commander Richard G. Dickerson, plane commander of lead plane, Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, Commander Task Force Forty Three, Commander George R. Kelly, Commanding Officer Air Development Squadron (VX-6), and Lieutenant Commander William B. Kurlak, plane commander of second plane; slide 3: Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, Lowell Thomas and pilots of VX-6 discuss plans for the non-stop flight by two LC-130s from Cape Town to McMurdo Station, Antarctica. Left to right: Lieutenant Commander Richard G. Dickerson, Lowell Thomas, Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, Commander Task Force 43, Lieutenant Commander Donald E. Miller and Commander George R. Kelly, Commanding Officer of Air Development VX-6; slide 4: The two LC-130s of VX-6, Air Development Squadron, ready to taxi out for take-off for the non-stop flight from Cape Town to McMurdo Station, Antarctica; slide 5: LC-130 aircraft #148320 of Air Development Squadron VX-6 at Naval Air Station, Rota, Spain where two of the squadron planes stopped for a crew rest during the flight to McMurdo Station; slide 6: LC-130 #148318 sits at the end of the running in preparation for take-off on the non-stop flight from Cape Town to McMurdo Station, Antarctica; slide 7: Rear Admiral James R. Reedy and Lowell Thomas, circa 1950s - 1970s; 3 (Box 1592)
    - Beginning of Slides found with photographic prints: [Men in orange suits, standing in front of airplane], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas and four other men looking at map], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas and a man in uniform about to board an airplane], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Airplane on runway], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Airplane on runway, about to take off], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Airplane on runway, about to take off], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas standing next to another man in uniform in front of United States Navy airplane], 7
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-6: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica, 1962); slide 7: Lowell Thomas (broadcasting, circa 1970s); slide 8-12: Lowell Thomas (photographs from H. T. Cowling, circa 1950s); slide 13-15: Lowell Thomas (Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 1967); slide 14-18: Lowell Thomas (dogs, circa 1970s)], circa 1950s - 1970s; 4 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica, 1962): Lowell Thomas standing next to another person with their back turned], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica, 1962): Close-up of Lowell Thomas wearing a fur hat], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica, 1962): Lowell Thomas standing among ice], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica, 1962): Lowell Thomas sitting on ground, penguins around him], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica, 1962): Lowell Thomas petting a dog], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Antarctica, 1962): Close-up of Lowell Thomas's profile], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (broadcasting, circa 1970s): Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast from behind his desk], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (photographs from H. T. Cowling, circa 1950s): Lowell Thomas], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (photographs from H. T. Cowling, circa 1950s): Lowell Thomas], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (photographs from H. T. Cowling, circa 1950s): Lowell Thomas], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (photographs from H. T. Cowling, circa 1950s): Lowell Thomas], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (photographs from H. T. Cowling, circa 1950s): Lowell Thomas], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 1967: Lowell Thomas standing next to a sheriff], 13
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 1967: Lowell Thomas standing next to a sheriff and a woman], 14
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 1967: Lowell Thomas standing next to a sheriff], 15
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (dogs, circa 1970s): Lowell Thomas in a golf cart with his dog], 16
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (dogs, circa 1970s): Lowell Thomas in a golf cart with his dog], 17
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (dogs, circa 1970s): Lowell Thomas in a golf cart with his dog], 18
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-8: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973); slide 9-15: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated)], 5 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (portrait painting, circa 1973): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 13
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 14
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (ski painting, undated): Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 15
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-14: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964)], 6 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas and another man on skiis], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas with other people on skiis], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas with another man on skiis], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas skiing], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas skiing], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas sitting on a railing], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas standing between a man and a woman], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas talking with another man], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas and another man on skiis], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas talking to another man], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas and another man on skiis], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Lowell Thomas with four other people on skiis], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Close-up of Lowell Thomas's face], 13
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (skiing at Alta, Utah, circa 1964): Snowy mountain], 14
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1: Lowell Thomas (trip to Dharamsala, 1963); slide 2-3: Lowell Thomas (alone, circa 1970s); slide 4: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, circa 1950s); slide 5-9: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas at the American Academy of Achievement banquet, circa late 1970s); slide 10-11: Lowell Thomas (with two unidentified men, circa 1960s); slide 12: Lowell Thomas Home, circa 1964; slide 13: Lowell Thomas Remembers, set in South Carolina, circa 1970s], circa 1950s - 1970s; 7 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (trip to Dharamsala, 1963): Lowell Thomas and another man, wearing fur hats], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (alone, circa 1970s): Lowell Thomas sitting behind a desk], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (alone, circa 1970s): Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, circa 1950s): Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas at the American Academy of Achievement banquet, circa late 1970s): Lowell Thomas with Marianna Munn at a podium], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas at the American Academy of Achievement banquet, circa late 1970s): Lowell Thomas sitting next Marianna Munn], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas at the American Academy of Achievement banquet, circa late 1970s): Lowell Thomas sitting next Marianna Munn], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas at the American Academy of Achievement banquet, circa late 1970s): Lowell Thomas with Marianna Munn and three other people], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with Mrs. Marianna Munn Thomas at the American Academy of Achievement banquet, circa late 1970s): Lowell Thomas talking with two other people], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with two unidentified men, circa 1960s): Lowell Thomas standing with two men], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas (with two unidentified men, circa 1960s): Lowell Thomas standing with two men], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas Home, circa 1964: Sign on house that says "Lowell Thomas Boyhood - Home Museum"], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas Remembers, set in South Carolina, circa 1970s: Lowell Thomas on television screen], 13
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-2: cartoon ("That-a-way" caricature, undated); slide 3: Cinerama (Japan, 1957); slide 4-5: Mary Davis, undated; slide 6: Earthquake Park, Alaska, circa 1973; slide 7-12: The Explorers Club; slide 13-18: Golf, circa 1954], circa 1954 - 1973; 8 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: ("That-a-way" caricature, undated)], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: ("That-a-way" caricature, undated)], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cinerama (Japan, 1957), Lowell Thomas and another man sitting in a boat], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Mary Davis, undated], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Mary Davis with two other women, undated], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Earthquake Park, Alaska], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Explorers Club, painting of lions], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Explorers Club, sailboat on ocean], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Explorers Club, boat on water], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Explorers Club, ship on water], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Explorers Club, Astronaut on the moon], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Explorers Club, Three people holding a flying fox], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, scorecard ], 13
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, scorecard ], 14
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, house on golf course], 15
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, people having a picnic outside], 16
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, man with a chef's hat on, serving food], 17
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, man with a chef's hat on, serving food], 18
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-11: Golf, circa 1954; slide 12-14: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas (North Pole), 1957; slide 15-16: Marco Polo painting at Capital Cities Corporation, circa 1971; slide 17: Nepal (Lowell Thomas on elephant), 1957; slide 18: New Guinea, undated; slide 19: Poster promoting Lowell Thomas on WMT radio, 1951 (from Vern Hansen); slide 20: Doctor Gordon Powell, Reverand Graham, Governor of New South Wales and lady sending a salute to Lowell Thomas, circa 1963], 1951 - circa 1971; 9 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, picnic gathering], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, people getting food at a picnic], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, people sitting down enjoying a picnic], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, group of men talking at a picnic], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, Lowell Thomas and friends gathered around a picnic table], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, group of men enjoying a picnic], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, people eating at a picnic on a golf course], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, group of men enjoying a picnic on the golf course], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, group of men posing on the golf course], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, group of men posing on the golf course], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Golf, circa 1954, group of men posing on the golf course], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas, 1957, Lowell Thomas holding a boot while sitting next to a man], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas, 1957, Lowell Thomas and three other men holding a flag in front of an airplane], 13
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas, 1957, Lowell Thomas and three other men looking at a map], 14
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Marco Polo painting at Capital Cities Corporation, circa 1971, painting of a man holding up a pineapple in front of a throne], 15